[Music]
and security once again ladies and
gentlemen Sir Peter guys congratulations
to all about qualifiers to our to our
voyage - I thank insurance warriors many
congratulations attending a pigment ink
democratic here this evening to yourself
accountable we present to you the first
batch of everybody be assured second
ability by France
[Music]
Baby Boomers
tonight we bestow the special order to
Jason and mr. Barnes mr. so seldom
it is with great pride and honor that we
present to you the 32 noble men and
women have earned the splendid glory of
the President's Award
mr. Lippman we are proud and honored to
present to you the recipients of the
Chairman's Award the crowning glory of
bancassurance luminaries
[Music]
to you to us the security back and
better thank you
who has WD and changing the way people
feel about insurance 2017 is going to be
a great year for all of you individually
for us collectively as we stay strong
and sales from together 2017 has you out
like a short moment raise
[Music]